var hardLevel = [{
    "question": "At Dartmouth College in 1964 John Kemeny and Thomas Kurtz invented .... ?",
    "choices": ["ALGOL", "BASIC", "FORTRAN","CHAIN"],
    "correct": "BASIC"
}, {
    "question": "Complete this quote “Computers are useless. They can only give you -------” (Pablo Picasso)",
    "choices": ["numbers", "pictures", "headaches", "answers"],
    "correct": "answers"
}, {
    "question": "Who invented C++ ?",
    "choices": ["Larry Wall", "Anders Hejlsberg", "Bjarne Stroustrup", "Alan Cooper"],
    "correct": "Bjarne Stroustrup"
}, {
    "question": "Which of these is not a functional programming language",
    "choices": ["F#", "Erlang", "Fortran", "Miranda"],
    "correct": "Fortran"
}, {
    "question": "Dylan, Erlang, Haskell and ML are examples of ... ?",
    "choices": ["web languages", "declarative languages", "functional languages", "visual languages"],
    "correct": "functional languages"
}, {
    "question": "A true or false statement put into code that the programmer expects to always be true is an ...?",
    "choices": ["exception", "harness", "assertion", "expression"],
    "correct": "assertion"

}, {
    "question": "EBNF is ...",
    "choices": ["Extensible Book Notation Format", "a replacement for the SAX XML parser", "a syntax for defining grammar", "the leader of the free software foundation"],
    "correct": "a syntax for defining grammar"

}, {
    "question": "A section of code that responds to a particular interaction of the user with a gui control is called a ... ?",
    "choices": ["dispatch function", "event handler", "Control structure", "exception handler"],
    "correct": "event handler"

}, {
    "question": "RISC is ...?",
    "choices": ["a defensive programming style", "a web framework", "a threading library", "a CPU design strategy"],
    "correct": "a CPU design strategy"

}, {
    "question": "You could use XSLT to ..?",
    "choices": ["speed up database queries", "encrypt passwords", "transform XML into HTML", "cache html pages"],
    "correct": "transform XML into HTML"
}];

quiz(hardLevel);